README
      In this README file, it is assumed that you have already gone through the setup process written in manual.pdf. In the case of encountering difficulties during the installation process, please go through manual.pdf again for detailed instructions and retry the installation. It is advised to familiarize yourself with the haptic device first by exploring the demos provided by 3D Systems.
Getting started:
1. Connect and calibrate the Haptic Touch device to the computer. Open “Touch Smart Setup” with the haptic device connected to the computer. The program should show an animated device synced with the haptic device in the middle of the window. Insert the stylus into the inkwell and click “Save Configuration” on the bottom of the window. For more details about the calibration process, check pages 8 and 9 of manual.pdf
2. Launch the Dentist Demo project in Unity and check for any errors. If there are issues with the code, compilation error messages with red hazard signs will be displayed in the console. It is recommended not to modify the code and utilize it as provided to ensure successful program execution on the first attempt. 
3. Run the Dentist Demo SampleScene in Unity by clicking the play button on the top of the window. Move the haptic device stylus around to see if the stylus in game is moving in sync. Occasionally, the haptic device may disconnect on its own, leading to a lack of feedback. If this occurs, wait for a few moments and rerun the program. Ensure that the haptic device is securely plugged in.
4. 
Features of the Dentist Demo:
1. Teeth Pulling: Approach the teeth and gums, and make contact with the haptic touch device. Feedback should be felt in the haptic device. After confirming the feedback, click the dark gray button on the stylus to grab the teeth. Slowly attempt to pull the teeth, and the force in the stylus should be felt. The amount of force feedback can be visualized using the gizmos feature in Unity.
2. Cavity Cleaning: When the stylus is touching the cavity, the black cavity will be drilled until it disappears. No additional actions are required in this case; simply approaching the cavity activates the script. Vibration can be added to the cavity cleaning in future developments.
3. Camera Rotation: Moving the stylus to the left or right side of the scene will cause the camera to rotate in the respective direction. This is caused by Invisible walls on the right and left sides of the screen. If collision with these walls occurs, the respective arrow button will turn red, and the camera will begin to rotate.
